A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Program and Policy, SG 3.3 (A2009) FA494
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, Program and Policy, SG 3.3 (A2009)
1987-1995
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA494
3.93 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, R3902, R3903, and AS 9202
Arrangement
Records are arranged as received by accession, then further arranged primarily by Series.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Program and Policy files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 2009.
Conditions Governing Access
Records are open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact a RAC archivist.
Scope and Contents
Contains staff program files and grant administration files.
- AC.2009.006: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-1995; AC.2009.006; 1.2 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, R3902
  - Program and Policy - General, 900
    - POPULATION AND HEALTH OFFICERS FILES - HALSTEAD - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE, 1994-1995 (Box R3902)
    - POPULATION AND HEALTH OFFICERS FILES - HALSTEAD - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE, 1993 (Box R3902)
    - POPULATION AND HEALTH OFFICERS FILES - HALSTEAD - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE, 1991-1992 (Box R3902)
    - POPULATION AND HEALTH OFFICERS FILES - HALSTEAD - IMMUNOBIOLOGY PATHOGENESIS OF PERSISTENT VIRUS INFECTIONS - KEN HERMANN, 1992 October 24-28 (Box R3902)
    - POPULATION AND HEALTH OFFICERS FILES - HALSTEAD - AMERICAN INSTITUTE OF BIOLOGYCAL SCIENCES - Washington, D.C., 1992 October 4-7 (Box R3902)
    - POPULATION AND HEALTH OFFICERS FILES - HALSTEAD - DENGUE VACCINE DEVELOPMENT, BANGKOK, THAILAND, 1992 August 24-26 (Box R3902)
    - POPULATION AND HEALTH OFFICERS FILES - HALSTEAD - CHINESE MEDICAL ASSOCIATION - TAPAI, TAIWAN, 1992 June 9-15 (Box R3902)
    - POPULATION AND HEALTH OFFICERS FILES - HALSTEAD - AMERICAN HEALTH CENTERS (AHC) - MEETING - WASHINGTON, D.C., 1992 June 2 (Box R3902)
    - POPULATION AND HEALTH OFFICERS FILES - HALSTEAD - INTERNATIONAL CENTERS FOR TROPICAL DISEASE RESEARCH -BETHESDA, MD - MICH. GOTTLIEB, 1992 April 29-30; May 1 (Box R3902)
    - POPULATION AND HEALTH OFFICERS FILES - HALSTEAD - NETWORK OF THE BIOLOGY OF PARASITE VECTORS - SANTA CRUZ, CALIFORNIA, 1992 April 2-5 (Box R3902)
    - POPULATION AND HEALTH OFFICERS FILES - HALSTEAD - ROCKVILLE, MD - AVEG -AIDS VACCINE SELECTION GROUP, 1992 February 21 (Box R3902)
    - POPULATION AND HEALTH OFFICERS FILES - HALSTEAD - DEVELOPMENT OF DENGUE VACCINE VIRUS - BANGKOK, THAILAND, 1991 August 26-28 (Box R3902)
    - POPULATION AND HEALTH OFFICERS FILES - HALSTEAD - DR. DAVID MORES (Box R3902)
    - POPULATION AND HEALTH OFFICERS FILES - HALSTEAD - HEALTH CHILD SURVIVAL FELLOWS PROGRAM, 1992 (Box R3902)
- AC.2009.016: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-1992; AC,2009.016; 1.2 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, R3903.
  - Program and Policy - General, 900
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) -, 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - ECO-LINK (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - ECO-TOURISM (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - IN ACADEMIC INSTITUTIONS (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - ETHICS AND AGRICULTURAL SCIENCE (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - ARTS (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - BUGET REQUEST (S), 1990 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - CONSULTANTS (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - DOCKET (S), 1991 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - ECONOMICS (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - GENERAL (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - THE GREEN COLLEGE (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - HARVARD SEMINAR ON ENVIRONMENTAL VALUES (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - AH/GE JOINT GUIDELINE (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - GUIDELINE IDEAS (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - GUIDELINE III (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - HUMAN DIMENSTION ON GLOBAL... (S), 1990 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - INDIGENIOUS PEOPLE'S CONFERENCE (S), 1990 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - LEAD PROGRAM (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - ETHICS IN MUSEUMS REPORT (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - JESSE SMITH NOYES FOUNDATION (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - RIO 1992 CONFERENCE/ETHICS AND ECONOMICS (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - RIO 1992 CONFERENCE/SPIRITUALITY (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - RIO 1992 CONFERENCE/WOMEN (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - TROPICAL FOREST HISTORY (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - ENVIRONMENTAL INITIATIVES IN SCIENCE (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - SURVEY OF BIODIVERSITY AND CULTURAL HERITAGE SITES (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - WORLD WOMEN'S CONFERENCE (S), 1991 (Box R3903)
    - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAM - ENVIRONMENTAL ETHICS (EE) - MARK SAGOFF - CONSULTANCY (S), 1990-1992 (Box R3903)
- AC.2009.060: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1987-1989; AC.2009.060; 1.2 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, AS 9202.
  - Program and Policy - Agriculture, 923
    - AGRICULTURE - P, 1987-1988 (Box AS 9202)
    - AGRICULTURE - P, 1989 (Box AS 9202)
    - AGRICULTURE - P, 1985-1987 (Box AS 9202)
    - AGRICULTURE - P, 1988 (Box AS 9202)
    - AGRICULTURE - P, 1989 (Box AS 9202)